<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>amazed by the noise - friendss-closing</title><link href="https://blog.nilleb.com/" rel="alternate"></link><link href="https://blog.nilleb.com/feeds/friendss-closing.atom.xml" rel="self"></link><id>https://blog.nilleb.com/</id><updated>2007-08-28T00:00:00+02:00</updated><entry><title>"friends’s closing"</title><link href="https://blog.nilleb.com/friendss-closing.html" rel="alternate"></link><published>2007-08-28T00:00:00+02:00</published><updated>2007-08-28T00:00:00+02:00</updated><author><name>nilleb - Ivo Bellin Salarin</name></author><id>tag:blog.nilleb.com,2007-08-28:/friendss-closing.html</id><summary type="html">&lt;h2&gt;- "thoughts"&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is the official announce, stating the death of the Friends Mailing List.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Friends is dead of an announced death. Some events in the past had undermined its health, and the health of its mantainer. Some reasons follow to better explain this choice.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;*. the principal aim was to keep …&lt;/p&gt;</summary><content type="html">&lt;h2&gt;- "thoughts"&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is the official announce, stating the death of the Friends Mailing List.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Friends is dead of an announced death. Some events in the past had undermined its health, and the health of its mantainer. Some reasons follow to better explain this choice.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;*. the principal aim was to keep in touch with far away friends. no success, since we all finished to talk about free software and open standards. flaming others, who wanted to share their experiences.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;*. "people who are not willing to flame others, do not flame others." If this phrase didn't come from the mouth of the principal flamer, I could have not thought it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;*. "sorry, I have no time at the moment to answer." but you've answered, so you had the time. what's wrong with adding two lines, which tell how you are?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;*. "perhaps I will answer while having a good pint with you." Nothing wrong about the pint. I like very much pints. I have them with the persons I can have a pint with. but perhaps, if I am writing on this fucking ML, that's because I am miles away from your fucking pint. and since there's no way for you to come here (where I am), this fucking pint will probably have to wait for a long time. is this a natural aspect of "keeping in touch"?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;*. unhappily, a great part of the mailing list ended to receive only messages, and to not participate to ingoing discussions&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;*. more unhappily, another great part of the mailing list didn't participate since years&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Technical questions as well have caused the end of the ML, so one reason more to switch, for those who are wishing to.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As you can see, I cannot continue wasting my stomach while maintaining a ML whose name is sanctimoniously "Friends". Thus, it has come the time to close. I will keep in touch with other media. With the eople who I can keep in touch with and I like to keep in touch with.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;friends was "easy". No more easy ways (for me) to reach other people. perhaps, this can help fortify relations.&lt;/p&gt;</content><category term="friendss-closing"></category></entry></feed>