<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>amazed by the noise - how-to-contract-a-pacs-being-a-stranger-in-france-still-incomplete</title><link href="https://blog.nilleb.com/" rel="alternate"></link><link href="https://blog.nilleb.com/feeds/how-to-contract-a-pacs-being-a-stranger-in-france-still-incomplete.atom.xml" rel="self"></link><id>https://blog.nilleb.com/</id><updated>2007-11-16T00:00:00+01:00</updated><entry><title>"How to contract a PACS being a stranger in France [still incomplete]"</title><link href="https://blog.nilleb.com/how-to-contract-a-pacs-being-a-stranger-in-france-still-incomplete.html" rel="alternate"></link><published>2007-11-16T00:00:00+01:00</published><updated>2007-11-16T00:00:00+01:00</updated><author><name>nilleb - Ivo Bellin Salarin</name></author><id>tag:blog.nilleb.com,2007-11-16:/how-to-contract-a-pacs-being-a-stranger-in-france-still-incomplete.html</id><summary type="html">&lt;h2&gt;- "thoughts"&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Note: all the informations below have been obtained going to the Tribunal d'Instance de Lyon in a date anterior to 1 November 2007. This tribunal is in rue Servient, 67, 69003 Lyon. To find the Tribunal next to your home, use the justice.gouv.fr site.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Well, if you …&lt;/p&gt;</summary><content type="html">&lt;h2&gt;- "thoughts"&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Note: all the informations below have been obtained going to the Tribunal d'Instance de Lyon in a date anterior to 1 November 2007. This tribunal is in rue Servient, 67, 69003 Lyon. To find the Tribunal next to your home, use the justice.gouv.fr site.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Well, if you want to contract a PACS, then the following steps should be sufficient for a young european citizen who (1) hasn't had problems with the law and (2) has not yet contracted a wedding or another PACS. Under these conditions, the documents you need to obtain are the following.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Acte de naissance - go to servicepublic.fr or to wikipedia.fr and understand what a PACS is and which its effects are. - go home or ask somebody who still lives in your country an integral copy of your "Acte de naissance"; it is usually a certificate which includes some information about when and where you're born, and who are your parents. - (optionally) get an "extract de l'acte de naissance", translated in French. If you live in the European union you should obtain this document easily. This can help the Tribunal d'instance employees to close an eye about the missing translation of the integral copy of the Acte de naissance. - if you haven't the "extract de l'acte de naissance" (en français), then call your Tribunal d'Instance (see justice.gouv.fr) and obtain the list of translators for your language. Then pay one of them to translate your integral copy in french.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Certificat de NON PACS - obtain the formulaire CERFA (search on google) - read the notice about it (same page as above) - compile it - then write to the "Tribunal de grande instance de Paris" (TODO: include address) including this formulaire, a copy of your extract de l'acte de naissance en français or your translation of the Acte de naissance, a copy of your identity document, and an empty envelop which already has a post stamp sufficient for the delivery of a single sheet of paper. - a week will generally be sufficient to obtain this document. In the meanwhile, you can proceed to obtain the Certificat de non inscription au registre civil.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Certificat de non inscription au registre civil It is necessary if you live in France from more than one year. - write a document in which you ask for the Certificat de non inscription au registre civil. Notice that you must include your name, surname, date an place of birth and the ones of both your parents. your letter must be addressed to (TODO)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Declaration sur l'honneur which affirms that you're not relatives and that you set your common place of residence at the given address (your address).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Document d'identité Take a copy of your identity card/passport and add it to the stack of documents.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Now, you're done. You can directly go to the Tribunal d'Instance of your city/department (see again justice.gouv.fr) to complete the procedure. Call the Tribunal to know the opening hours of the guichet and the hours during which you can set up the PACS. Then expect a variable amount of time of wait, depending on the day, on the number of persons in the queue, and on the mood of the person at the guichet. (At least half a day, usually in the morning)&lt;/p&gt;</content><category term="how-to-contract-a-pacs-being-a-stranger-in-france-still-incomplete"></category></entry></feed>