<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>amazed by the noise - im-at-home</title><link href="https://nilleb.github.io/" rel="alternate"></link><link href="https://nilleb.github.io/feeds/im-at-home.atom.xml" rel="self"></link><id>https://nilleb.github.io/</id><updated>2007-08-19T00:00:00+02:00</updated><entry><title>"I’m at home"</title><link href="https://nilleb.github.io/im-at-home.html" rel="alternate"></link><published>2007-08-19T00:00:00+02:00</published><updated>2007-08-19T00:00:00+02:00</updated><author><name>nilleb - Ivo Bellin Salarin</name></author><id>tag:nilleb.github.io,2007-08-19:/im-at-home.html</id><summary type="html">&lt;h2&gt;- "thoughts"&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It' s raining outside, on this Sunday evening in Lyon. the rain has started some moments ago. it's the golden hour, and this strange light colour contributes making this moment special. I'm thinking about my life here. it's true, I feel at home. For so many things... I wouldn't …&lt;/p&gt;</summary><content type="html">&lt;h2&gt;- "thoughts"&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It' s raining outside, on this Sunday evening in Lyon. the rain has started some moments ago. it's the golden hour, and this strange light colour contributes making this moment special. I'm thinking about my life here. it's true, I feel at home. For so many things... I wouldn't know where to start to make my list.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Here, I feel a warm sensation. Perhaps it's its contrast with the sensations I feel elsewhere (that makes me sure that I'm at home).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This physical distance helps me to forget certain habits which permeate the society. Surely I'm generalizing, but there are so many noxious habits... And so many people, who are applying them to their lifestyles. And so many people, who are willing to see the noxious habits applied to other people. But now I'm descending in philosophical theories more that writing sensate sentences.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I think that I've found the right distance from my family members, except for the little Lucia. Now I'm able to live more intensely and more positively my parental relationships.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I would like to talk more, but the time to go prepare my dinner has come.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Side news: I got a portable computer, I've called it quenelle. After a day spent configuring it, it's suitable for most uses. I have spent this week end doing home works and swilling. And cooking, it's sure...&lt;/p&gt;</content><category term="im-at-home"></category></entry></feed>