<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>amazed by the noise - lastfm</title><link href="https://nilleb.github.io/" rel="alternate"></link><link href="https://nilleb.github.io/feeds/lastfm.atom.xml" rel="self"></link><id>https://nilleb.github.io/</id><updated>2008-01-17T00:00:00+01:00</updated><entry><title>"last.fm"</title><link href="https://nilleb.github.io/lastfm.html" rel="alternate"></link><published>2008-01-17T00:00:00+01:00</published><updated>2008-01-17T00:00:00+01:00</updated><author><name>nilleb - Ivo Bellin Salarin</name></author><id>tag:nilleb.github.io,2008-01-17:/lastfm.html</id><summary type="html">&lt;h2&gt;- "thoughts"&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;some days ago I received an email from a friend. she asked me to add her contact to my friends list on last.fm. it was since some years that I didn't use it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;well, I have been happy to discover it again, even if the site interface is …&lt;/p&gt;</summary><content type="html">&lt;h2&gt;- "thoughts"&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;some days ago I received an email from a friend. she asked me to add her contact to my friends list on last.fm. it was since some years that I didn't use it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;well, I have been happy to discover it again, even if the site interface is not so easy to browse (not so intuitive, I'd rather say).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;from a technical point of view, the traffic sent on the network is not so much, and the server transmission port is always the 80/HTTP. So, it's rather difficult to get blocked by some firewall/proxy.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;from a music fan point of view, it is a good radio. on this radio I can choose what to hear, and somebody has filled an huge database about artist similarities, so even when I do not know the name of the group, I can still find it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I believe in social networking, sometimes. I'm still waiting for a recommendation, but till now I have discovered so many known people on the network that I'm however happy about knowing their musical preferences.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;ianbsparrow is my nickname, in the case you choose to use it.&lt;/p&gt;</content><category term="lastfm"></category></entry></feed>