<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>amazed by the noise - the-last-weekend-of-august</title><link href="https://blog.nilleb.com/" rel="alternate"></link><link href="https://blog.nilleb.com/feeds/the-last-weekend-of-august.atom.xml" rel="self"></link><id>https://blog.nilleb.com/</id><updated>2007-09-12T00:00:00+02:00</updated><entry><title>"The last weekend of August"</title><link href="https://blog.nilleb.com/the-last-weekend-of-august.html" rel="alternate"></link><published>2007-09-12T00:00:00+02:00</published><updated>2007-09-12T00:00:00+02:00</updated><author><name>nilleb - Ivo Bellin Salarin</name></author><id>tag:blog.nilleb.com,2007-09-12:/the-last-weekend-of-august.html</id><summary type="html">&lt;h2&gt;- "thoughts"&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;[please note: I'm really late while writing this, thus the facts are related to the last week end of august rather than to the first of september...]&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;the last week end has been the opposite of relaxing. I don't want to speak about the new curtains we got during …&lt;/p&gt;</summary><content type="html">&lt;h2&gt;- "thoughts"&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;[please note: I'm really late while writing this, thus the facts are related to the last week end of august rather than to the first of september...]&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;the last week end has been the opposite of relaxing. I don't want to speak about the new curtains we got during the holidays, and which needed a long set-up time on saturday. I'd more like to talk about the saturday evening, or about the sunday in its entirety. Saturday evening we had Nacira at home, and we spent with her some happy hours. we cooked some italian food, principally seafood and pasta, in the way turinese people are able to prepare it :-) Sunday morning we have taken our things, food and "technical sportswear" to have a trip on the french hillside. We have chosen the trip with our friends Roselyn and Benoit. And at the dawn of 11 o'clock we leaved Lyon in favour of Yzeron, in the "ouest Lyonnais". I won't tell you how much Yzeron and its surrounding hills are beautiful. (this, because I wish you to see them yourself. If you live in Lyon, the trip to Yzeron takes 45 minutes by car. a small hike to the Yzeron falls takes about 45 minutes.) I won't tell you about the fact we have lost our path and we have finished our trip in a ... imaginative way, but tasting really good croissants and drinking some sweet "brevage". Really nice weekend. I have liked it sooooo much! :-)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Thanks a lot, Nacira, Roselyn and Benoit. :-)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Some links for the internet-only travellers, and for all those who would like to see the landscape before going to Yzeron.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://fr.wikipedia.org/wiki/Yzeron"&gt;Wikipedia: Yzeron&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://maps.google.fr/maps?f=q&amp;amp;hl=fr&amp;amp;geocode=&amp;amp;q=yzeron&amp;amp;sll=47.15984,2.988281&amp;amp;sspn=10.444166,20.566406&amp;amp;ie=UTF8&amp;amp;ll=45.711454,4.590311&amp;amp;spn=0.010473,0.020084&amp;amp;t=h&amp;amp;z=16&amp;amp;om=1"&gt;Google Maps: Yzeron&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</content><category term="the-last-weekend-of-august"></category></entry></feed>